techtutshub.com 2012-12-12

# Privacy Policy

At [ **Techtutshub**](http://www.techtutshub.com/ "Techtutshub") ** ** the  **privacy**  of our visitors is extremely important.  This _**Privacy Policy**_ outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this **_Privacy Policy_.**

> **Note:** The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

###  Log Files

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  *  Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  *  Types of browser
  *  Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  *  Date and time stamp
  *  Referring and exit pages
  *  Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

###  Cookies.

**www.techtutshub.com**  does not use cookies.

**www.techtutshubcom**  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  

###  Distribution of Information.

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: 

  * Permitted or required by law; or, 
  * Trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or,
  * Investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing Purposes.

###  Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance.

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least  **13 years old or older.**

###  Commitment to Data Security.

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

###  Our License Details

Techtutshub by [Hammad Baig](http://www.techtutshub.com/) is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/deed.en_US).  
Based on a work at <http://www.techtutshub.com/>.

###  Privacy Contact Information.

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing  email address to receive Latest Updates from [Techtutshub](http://www.techtutshub.com/).. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you have any  **Questions, Concerns, or Comments**  about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:  
E-mail:  **w** **eb** **master@techtutshub.com**   – [ **Contact Us**](http://techtutshub.com/p/contact-us.html "Contact Us")    
Last Updated: August 7 , 2012
